strangecosmos.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

Online Privacy Statement

StrangeCosmos.com respects the privacy of visitors to our site. Please read this Privacy Statement carefully so that you understand our privacy practices relating to information we gather through this website. Other policies may apply to information we gather elsewhere. Questions regarding privacy issues should be directed to StrangeCosmos.com at: privacy@StrangeCosmos.com. 

THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT 

The information gathered through this website falls into two categories: (1) information voluntarily supplied by visitors to our website through optional registration or e-commerce transactions, and (2) tracking information gathered as visitors navigate through our site. Third party service providers on or linked to by our website, such as vendors of products and services offered through our site, may be gathering information, as well. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

To make use of certain features on our website (such as contests, surveys, message boards, music download functionality, customizable audio applications, and others) visitors need to register and to provide certain information as part of the registration process. We may also ask visitors for certain information in connection with the purchase of products/services on our website. (We may ask, for example, for your name, email address, sex, age, zip code and credit card information, and we might request information on your interest in concerts, different types of music and the like.) The information you supply will help us to offer you more personalized features, to tailor our site to your interests, to make the site more useful to you, and to process your e-commerce transactions. 

The more you tell us about yourself, the more value we can offer you. Supplying such information is entirely voluntary. But if you don't supply the information we need, we may be unable to provide you with services we make available to other visitors to our site. And we can't send you email alerting you to a new service we're offering, to concerts scheduled for your area, or to upcoming personal appearances by our on-air personalities if you don't tell us what you're interested in and give us your email address. Similarly, we can't notify you that you've been lucky enough to win a prize in a promotional contest if we don't know how to contact you. 

If you want to remain completely anonymous, you're still free to take advantage of the wealth of content available on our site without registration. 

Bi-Weekly e-letter 

StrangeCosmos.com offers electronic e-letters to users. StrangeCosmos.com gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. You may opt-out of receiving future electronic e-letters by sending an email to the address provided in each mailer or directly to info@strangecosmos.com. 

StrangeCosmos.com delivers e-letters, marketing and product offerings via email to registered recipients from our subscription center.? 

Choice / Opt-out 

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving direct mail and/or electronic communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives the users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future electronic communications: 

Follow the unsubscribe instructions included with each e-letter. 

Send a blank e-mail to the appropriate address below:1) StrangeCosmos - remove@strangecosmos.com 

COOKIES 

To help make our site more responsive to the needs of our visitors, we invoke a standard feature of browser software, called a "cookie," to assign each visitor a unique number, a sort of user ID, if you will, that resides on your computer. The cookie doesn't actually identify the visitor, just the computer that a visitor uses to access our site. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), we won't know who you are, even if we assign a cookie to your computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply. A cookie can't read unrelated data off your hard drive. Our advertisers and third party service providers may also assign their own cookies to your browser, a process that we don't control. 

We use cookies to help us tailor our site to your needs, to deliver a better, more personalized service. For example, cookies help us to recognize you as a return visitor, which provides convenience for you. Once you've signed up for one contest or participated in one survey, for example, you can sign up for subsequent website contests or surveys using "one-click entering." We also use cookies to avoid showing you the same ad, repeatedly, during a single visit. In addition, we may use cookies to track which pages on our site are most frequently visited by our users. We can build a better site if we know which pages our users are visiting and how often. Of course, you can set your browser not to accept cookies, but if you do, you may not be able to take advantage of the personalized features enjoyed by other visitors to our site. 

BROWSER LEVEL INFORMATION 

Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer configuration when you visit our site, including the type of browser software you use and your IP address. (Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data -- such as the web pages you view.) Your IP address does not identify you personally. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our site to the interests of our users, and to measure traffic within our site. 

SWEEPSTAKES AND OTHER PROMOTIONS 

From time to time, we may offer sweepstakes or other promotions on our website. If you enter a sweepstakes or promotional contest, we'll ask you to provide information about yourself (such as your name, address, and email address). Among other things, we'll need this information to contact you if you win. We may share this information with any co-sponsor of the contest or sweepstakes, which we'll identify in the contest rules. If you don't want us to collect the information requested in the contest or sweepstakes registration form or to provide it to co-sponsors, please do not enter the contest or sweepstakes. 

INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THIRD PARTIES 

To make our site more valuable to our visitors, we offer some features in conjunction with other providers. Our message board services, for example, are made available through cooperative arrangements with providers that specialize in operating such services. Our site includes links to plenty of other websites, and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy practices we don't control. When you access another website, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy statement of the operator of that site. And when you provide information in the course of obtaining products or services through our site, use of any information you provide may be governed by the privacy policy of the provider of those products or services, even if it appears that you're on Cox Radio-branded pages throughout the transaction. The provider's privacy policy may differ from ours. If you can't find the privacy statement of any of our provider partners via a link either from the site's homepage or from the pages on which the products or services are offered, you should contact the provider directly for more information. We use a third-party advertising company - FastClick -- to serve ads when you visit our website. FastClick does not use your name, address, email address, or phone number to deliver Internet ads. FastClick does use information about your browser and Web surfing to determine which ads to show you. If you would like more information about FastClick's practices proceed to FastCLick.com 

Third Party Advertising 

We use MaxWorldwide and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please go here here: 

Third Party Cookies 

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique ?cookie? on your browser. 

DISCLOSURES 

When we present information to our advertisers -- to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our websites -- it is usually in the form of aggregated statistics on traffic to various pages within our site. From time to time, we may share either individual or aggregated information on visitors to our site with third parties that provide services on or are linked to by our website, and with those marketing products and services that we believe may be of interest to you. For example, when a provider promotes its products or services through our website, we may collect your contact information on the provider's behalf, through a form on our website. If you provide us your email address, from time to time we may send you emails about products, services, or events that we believe may be of interest to you. Though we hope you'll find these emails informative and useful, if you do not wish to receive such emails, please indicate, when you give us your email address, that you'd prefer not to receive them. You can also unsubscribe by following the simple unsubscribe instructions included with each email. 

OTHER DISCLOSURES 

We may occasionally release information about our visitors when release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce our Visitor Agreement, or to protect the rights, property or safety of visitors to our site, our customers, the public, or a related company. As our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. If our assets are acquired by another company, information on visitors to our website would be among the transferred assets. 

SECURITY 

Information gathered on our website is stored within StrangeCosmos.com controlled databases (or databases hosted on our behalf) on servers maintained in protected environments. However, no physical or electronic security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our servers or databases, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. And, of course, any information you post to any message board or other public posting area is available to anyone with Internet access. If you don't want people to know your email address, for example, don't include it in any message you post publicly. 

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT 

If we change our privacy policy at some point in the future, we will post the changes before they take effect. If at any point we decide to use personally identifying information in a manner different from what was stated at the time the information was collected, we will notify you and give you an opportunity to opt out of the proposed use. 

DISCLAIMER

All the pictures, videos and games shown on StrangeCosmos.com are the property of their respective owners. All the pictures, videos and games contained on any StrangeCosmos Family sites (see list on all sides and site bottom) were collected from different public sources, including different websites, considered to be in public domain. Images posted are believed to be posted within our rights according to the U.S. Copyright Fair Use Act (title 17, U.S. Code.) StrangeCosmos.com does not claim to own exclusive rights on all images and videos published. All sources we use to create our articles are and will be credited with a proper link back. However, we are hosting a lot of uncredited material from unknown authors we received via mails, from friends and our readers. If you own copyrights to some material such as images or data and you want us to remove it from our pages, contact us using the Contact Us Tab via the link at the top Navigation bar to claim your ownership and we will either credit you and your website, or if you wish – completely remove the content.
